Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - M
        - Maestro Fresh Wes - Another funky break (from my pap's crate), 1992; SR-19739; Maestro Fresh Wes (Box 345)
          Catalog # 865 677-1; A-side Matrix # 865-677-1-AS
          Polydor
        - M.A.F. X-Perience - Dreamland, 1994; SR-19740; M.A.F. X-Perience (Box 345)
          Catalog # DOS 011-1; A-side Matrix # DOS-011-A1
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Mafia - All night long, 1990; SR-19741; Mafia; Baron, Lisa (Box 345)
          Catalog # MMX 1; A-side Matrix # MMX 1 A1
          Mafia Records
        - Mafia - ABC | Gismo, 1988; SR-19742; Mafia; J.F.K. (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19743. 2 copies.
          Catalog # BBH-1; A-side Matrix # BBH 1 A
        - Mafia - ABC | Gismo, 1988; SR-19743; Mafia; J.F.K. (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19742. 2 copies.
        - Mafioso Crime Family - Autobahn, 1998; SR-19744; Mafioso Crime Family (Box 345)
          Catalog # MBK-001; A-side Matrix # MBK-001-A
          MBK Records
        - Mag - How u like it, 1998; SR-19745; Mag (Box 345)
          Catalog # RPROLP0834; A-side Matrix # RPROLP- 0834 A
        - Maggotron Crushing Crew - Miami's rockin' baby (Miami jams), 1991; SR-19746; Maggotron Crushing Crew (Box 345)
          Catalog # PD-068; A-side Matrix # PD-068-A C1
          Pandisc
        - Magic - That's me, 1999; SR-19747; Magic (Box 345)
          Catalog # SPRO 81259; A-side Matrix # 08724 81259-1-A
          No Limit Records
        - Magic - Ice on my wrist, 1999; SR-19748; Magic (Box 345)
          Catalog # SPRO 81270; A-side Matrix # S-41886
        - Magic City - Let's rock, 1979; SR-19749; Magic City; Fire (Box 345)
          Catalog # SSD-209; A-side Matrix # SSD-209 R1-AX
          Sunshine Sound Disco
        - Magic City - Let's rock, 1979; SR-19750; Magic City; Fire (Box 345)
        - Magic Lady - Sexy body, 1982; SR-19751; Magic Lady (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19752. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP-17198; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 017198B-T2
        - Magic Lady - Sexy body, 1982; SR-19752; Magic Lady (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19751. 2 copies.
        - Magical Sol Brothas - Yeah!, 1996; SR-19753; Magical Sol Brothas (Box 345)
          Catalog # 12-PO 365; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-365 SIDE 1
          Knappy Head Entertainment
          Houston, Texas
        - Magnetic Pulstar - Secret love, 1996; SR-19754; Magnetic Pulstar (Box 345)
          Catalog # DOS 031; A-side Matrix # DOS 031-A1
        - Magnetic Pulstar - Pulse, 1995; SR-19755; Magnetic Pulstar (Box 345)
          Catalog # DOS 017-1; A-side Matrix # DO 017-A
        - Magnetic Touch - You deserve it, SR-19756; Magnetic Touch (Box 345)
          Catalog # C-0001; A-side Matrix # C-0001-A
          Cheryl Records
        - Magnetic Touch - Stay with me my love, SR-19757; Magnetic Touch (Box 345)
          Catalog # C-1009; A-side Matrix # C-1009-A
        - Magnificent Three - Crush, 1984; SR-19758; Magnificent Three; Fearless Master (Box 345)
          Catalog # C.C.L. 102; A-side Matrix # CCL-102-A
          C.C.L. Records
        - Magnusson, Anneli - Smile 'n' shine, 1997; SR-19759; Magnusson, Anneli (Box 345)
          Catalog # MCA8P 4101; A-side Matrix # MCA 13059
        - Mahavishnu Orchestra - Inner worlds, 1976; SR-19760; Mahavishnu Orchestra; McLaughlin, John (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19761. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PC 33908; A-side Matrix # AL-33908-1C
        - Mahavishnu Orchestra - Inner worlds, 1976; SR-19761; Mahavishnu Orchestra; McLaughlin, John (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19760. 2 copies.
        - Mahavishnu Orchestra - Apocolypse, 1974; SR-19762; Mahavishnu Orchestra; London Symphony Orchestra; Thomas, Michael Tilson (Box 345)
          Catalog # KC 32957; A-side Matrix # P AL 32957-1H
        - Mahlon - Erica, 1995; SR-19763; Mahlon (Box 345)
          Catalog # OP-221; A-side Matrix # OP221-1A
          Optic Records
        - Mahogany - Ride on the rhythm, 1982; SR-19764; Mahogany; Watkins, Bernice (Box 345)
          Catalog # WES 22150; A-side Matrix # WES-22150A-1A
          West End Records
        - Mai Tai - Turn your love around, 1986; SR-19765; Mai Tai (Box 345)
          Catalog # 888-355-1; A-side Matrix # 8883551-AS
          Mercury
        - Maia, Tim - Tim Maia Racional Vol. 2, 2011; SR-19766; Maia, Tim (Box 345)
          Catalog # 88697853812; A-side Matrix # 004/75
          Abril Coleções
          Rio De Janiero, Brazil
        - Maia, Tim - Sossego, 1991; SR-19767; Maia, Tim (Box 345)
          Catalog # 670.9378; A-side Matrix # 670.9378-A
          WEA
        - Maia, Tim - Tim Maia, 1970; SR-19768; Maia, Tim (Box 345)
          Catalog # LPNG 44.053; A-side Matrix # 200-44053-A
          Brazil
        - Main Attraction - Rainy night, 1986; SR-19769; Main Attraction (Box 345)
          Catalog # JW-14400; A-side Matrix # PW-14400 A-1
        - Main One: The Ghetto Child - Check da skillz, 1995; SR-19770; Main One: The Ghetto Child (Box 345)
          Catalog # 25041-1; A-side Matrix # 25041-1 A
        - Main One - It's on, 1996; SR-19771; Main One (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19772. 2 copies.
          Catalog # MO-001; A-side Matrix # MO-001-A
          Main One Recordings
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Main One - It's on, 1996; SR-19772; Main One (Box 345)
          In same jacket as # SR-19771. 2 copies.
        - Main One: The Ghetto Child - Check da skillz, 1995; SR-19773; Main One: The Ghetto Child (Box 345)
        - Main Source - Breaking atoms, 1991; SR-19774; Main Source (Box 345)
          Catalog # WPL 2004; A-side Matrix # WP-2004-A
          Wild Patch
        - Main Source - Peace is not the word to play, 1991; SR-19775; Main Source (Box 345)
          Catalog # V-56229; A-side Matrix # V-1-56229-Z2
        - Main Source - Fakin' the funk, 1992; SR-19776; Main Source (Box 345)
          Catalog # Y-56251; A-side Matrix # Y-56251-A Z1
        - Major Figgas - Yeah that's us; Y'all can't f**k with da figgas, SR-19777; Major Figgas (Box 345)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # MAJOR FIGGAS -A
          Ruff Wax
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Major Mackeral - Don bon; Gimme punash, 1987; SR-19778; Major Mackeral (Box 345)
          Catalog # Vibes 011; A-side Matrix # VIBES 011 A
          Vibes
          Riverdale, Maryland
        - Major Mackeral - Labba mouth, 1994; SR-19779; Major Mackeral (Box 345)
          Catalog # RB 0008; A-side Matrix # RB 0008-A
          Rude Boy Records
        - Major Mackeral - The show down, SR-19780; Major Mackeral (Box 345)
          Catalog # TY-061; A-side Matrix # TY-061-A
          Tan-Yah
        - Major Stress - More and more; A day in the Stuy, 1995; SR-19781; Major Stress (Box 345)
          Catalog # NR-001; A-side Matrix # NR001-A
          Norfside Records
        - Makay - Hands, 2003; SR-19782; Makay (Box 345)
          Catalog # NL 082; A-side Matrix # NL 082-A
          No Label
          Italy
        - Makeba, Miriam - In concert, 1967; SR-19783; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # RS 6253; A-side Matrix # RS 6253 A
          Reprise Records
        - Makeba, Miriam - Pata pata, 1968; SR-19784; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # RLP 77.012; A-side Matrix # 6274 A
        - Makeba, Miriam - In concert, 1968; SR-19785; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # R 6253; A-side Matrix # 10661 1C R-6253A
        - Makeba, Miriam - Pata pata, 1967; SR-19786; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # RS 6274; A-side Matrix # RS-6274
        - Makeba, Miriam - Sangoma, 1988; SR-19787; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # 1-25673; A-side Matrix # 1 25673 A DMM
          Warner Bros Records
        - Makeba, Miriam - African convention, 1980; SR-19788; Makeba, Miriam (Box 345)
          Catalog # 88 199; A-side Matrix # 88 199 A
          Pläne
        - Makeba, Miriam - The voice of Africa, 1964; SR-19789; Makeba, Miriam (Box 346)
          Catalog # LPM 2845; A-side Matrix # PHRM-6384--3S
        - Makesome Breaksome - Rew'd, 1999; SR-19790; Makesome Breaksome (Box 346)
          Catalog # plank011; A-side Matrix # PLANK-011-A
          Plank Records
        - Makossa, Jack E - The opera house, 1987; SR-19791; Makossa, Jack E (Box 346)
          Catalog # 2; A-side Matrix # MINIMAL-2-A
          Minimal Records
        - Malaika - So much love, 1992; SR-19792; Malaika (Box 346)
          Catalog # AMX 0084; A-side Matrix # AMX 0084 A1
          A&M PM
        - Malaysa - I don't give a damn, 2003; SR-19793; Malaysa (Box 346)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 7945-MALAYSIA-1(A)
          Mae Dae Records
        - Malcolm X - The last message, SR-19794; Malcolm X (Box 346)
          Catalog # MX-101; A-side Matrix # MX 103 3-10 71
          Charisma Records
        - Malik (Mad Lyrics) - No more 9 to 5, 1994; SR-19795; Malik (Mad Lyrics) (Box 346)
          Catalog # 13964764; A-side Matrix # 13964764-AA
          MPacked Sounds
          Trenton, New Jersey
        - Malone, Debbie - Rescue me, 1989; SR-19796; Malone, Debbie (Box 346)
          Catalog # KRZ 001; A-side Matrix # KRZ001A2
          Krunch
        - Malopoets - Sound of the people, 1985; SR-19797; Malopoets (Box 346)
          Catalog # V-7859-1; A-side Matrix # V-1-7859-P-1
        - Mami, Cheb - Parisien Du Nord; Marseillais Du Nord, 1998; SR-19798; Mami, Cheb (Box 346)
          Catalog # 7243 8 85556 8; A-side Matrix # 072438955586-A
        - MAW - Ekabo | Elements of life (unreleased mixes), 2000; SR-19799; MAW; Vega, Little Louie (Box 346)
          Catalog # MAW-053; A-side Matrix # MAW-053-A
          MAW Records
          Union City, New Jersey
        - Man Parrish - Brown sugar, 1987; SR-19800; Man Parrish (Box 346)
          Catalog # FMS 62282; A-side Matrix # FMS-62282-A
        - Man Parrish - Hip hop be bop (don't stop), 1996; SR-19801; Man Parrish (Box 346)
          Catalog # HCL 2294; A-side Matrix # HCL-2294-A
          Man Made Productions
        - Manaças, César - Sonhos De Paixão | Destino De Ser Feliz, 1995; SR-19802; Manaças, César; Primeira Via (Box 346)
          Catalog # 443.013; A-side Matrix # 443013 A
          Afegan
        - Managers - Shake it up, shake it up, 1982; SR-19803; Managers (Box 346)
          Catalog # SUN 401; A-side Matrix # SUNNYVIEW 401-A-33
          Sunnyview
        - Mandel, Mike - Utopia parkway, 1980; SR-19804; Mandel, Mike (Box 346)
          Catalog # VSD 79437; A-side Matrix # V SD794371-1B
          Vanguard Freestyle
        - Mandingo Brass - Ultimate mash-up, 1979; SR-19805; Mandingo Brass (Box 346)
          Catalog # MBLP-002; A-side Matrix # MB 1001-A
          Sauko Music
          San Juan, Puerto Rico
        - Mandrill - Put your money where the funk is, 1982; SR-19806; Mandrill (Box 346)
          In same jacket as # SR-19807. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 79902; A-side Matrix # S-79902-A
          Montage Records
        - Mandrill - Put your money where the funk is, 1982; SR-19807; Mandrill (Box 346)
          In same jacket as # SR-19806. 2 copies.
        - Mandrill - Wired for love, 1983; SR-19808; Mandrill (Box 346)
          Catalog # MS-606; A-side Matrix # MS-606-A
        - Mandrill - Fencewalk; Mango meat, 1973; SR-19809; Mandrill (Box 346)
          Catalog # URBX-38; A-side Matrix # URBX 38 A
          Urban
        - Manga, Bebe - Ami - Oyomiya, SR-19810; Manga, Bebe (Box 346)
          Catalog # SMP 6022; A-side Matrix # SMP 6022 A
          Star Musique
        - Mangione, Chuck - Feel so good, 1977; SR-19811; Mangione, Chuck (Box 346)
          Catalog # AM-8448; A-side Matrix # AM 9002 S-12 M1
        - Mangione, Chuck - The Chuck Mangione quartet, 1972; SR-19812; Mangione, Chuck (Box 346)
          Catalog # SRM-1-631; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-631A-M2
        - Mangual, José - Buyú, 1977; SR-19813; Mangual, José (Box 346)
          Catalog # T433; A-side Matrix # LPV-433-A
          Turnstyle Records
          Palisades Park, New Jersey
        - Mangwana, Sam - For ever, 1989; SR-19814; Mangwana, Sam; Franco; TP OK Jazz (Box 346)
          Catalog # 38775-1; A-side Matrix # 387751 A
          France
        - Manhattan Transfer - Boy from New York City, 1981; SR-19815; Manhattan Transfer (Box 346)
          Catalog # DMD 276; A-side Matrix # STDM 398061 1-2
        - Manhattans - Follow your heart, 1981; SR-19816; Manhattans (Box 346)
          Catalog # SS-8007; A-side Matrix # SS 8007 A
          Solid Smoke Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Manhunt - Tiamat war; Krypton, 1998; SR-19817; Manhunt (Box 346)
          Catalog # EARTH74; A-side Matrix # EARTH-74-A
          Tiamat World Entertainment
        - Maniac - 2deep 2peep, 1994; SR-19818; Maniac (Box 346)
          Catalog # 422860265-1; A-side Matrix # 42286-0265-1-A
          Crenshaw Blvd Records
        - Mann, Bobby - Body rockin' rap, 1980; SR-19819; Mann, Bobby (Box 346)
          Catalog # 12-1003; A-side Matrix # 12-1003-A
          Sheek Records
        - Manilow, Barry - Oh, Julie!, 1982; SR-19820; Manilow, Barry (Box 346)
          Catalog # AB 2500; A-side Matrix # AB-2500-SA
        - Maniquin - I wanna ride, 1989; SR-19821; Maniquin (Box 346)
          Catalog # 49 68218; A-side Matrix # XSS 68218B-1A
        - Mankind Liberation Front - Isolated, 1999; SR-19822; Mankind Liberation Front (Box 346)
          Catalog # COA 77148-1; A-side Matrix # COA-77148-A
          City Of Angels
        - Manley, Cynthia - Chain reaction; Love ain't easy, 1983; SR-19823; Manley, Cynthia (Box 346)
          Catalog # DMD 682; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45480-1
        - Mann, David - Games, 1987; SR-19824; Mann, David (Box 346)
          Catalog # 90628-1; A-side Matrix # ST-AN-879 491-B 1-1
          Antilles New Directions
        - Mannish - Expect that, 1995; SR-19825; Mannish (Box 346)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # EXPECT THAT S-31574
        - Mannoia, Fiorella - Canzioni per parlare, 1988; SR-19826; Mannoia, Fiorella (Box 346)
          Catalog # DDD 460801 1; A-side Matrix # DDD 460801-1 A
          DDD
        - Manor Park Rangers - That's right we're trickin', 1991; SR-19827; Manor Park Rangers (Box 346)
          Catalog # BA-6003; A-side Matrix # BA-6003-A C
          Breakaway Records
        - Manteca - Manteca, 1982; SR-19828; Manteca (Box 346)
          Catalog # 2393 321; A-side Matrix # 16 0 2393321 1 380 polygram
        - Mantra - Doin' it to the bone, 1981; SR-19829; Mantra (Box 346)
          Catalog # NBD 20234; A-side Matrix # NBD-20234-81-CS-137-PW1
          Casablanca
        - Mantronix - Bassline, 1986; SR-19830; Mantronix (Box 346)
          Catalog # SLX-0018X; A-side Matrix # SLX-0018X RE
          Sleeping Bag Records
        - Mantronix - Simple Simon (you gotta regard), 1988; SR-19831; Mantronix (Box 346)
          Catalog # V-15362; A-side Matrix # V-1-15362-100995A-995-Z1
          Capitol Records
        - Mantronix - Sing a song (break it down), 1987; SR-19832; Mantronix (Box 346)
          Catalog # V-15353; A-side Matrix # V-1 15353-100996A 996B Z2
        - Mantronix - Take your time, 1990; SR-19833; Mantronix (Box 346)
          Catalog # V-15579; A-side Matrix # V-1-15579-Z2
        - Mantronix - Needle to the groove, 1985; SR-19834; Mantronix (Box 346)
          Catalog # SLX-15; A-side Matrix # SLX-15Y
        - Mantus - Love is a natural thing, 1980; SR-19835; Mantus (Box 346)
          Catalog # SM 12-403; A-side Matrix # SM 12-403-A-1
          SMI Records
        - Mantus - I'm so in love with you, 1979; SR-19836; Mantus (Box 346)
          Catalog # SM-12-402; A-side Matrix # SMI-12-402 A
        - Manza - La Valse Des Pantins | Exclusif, 1999; SR-19837; Manza; Diamantaire (Box 346)
          Catalog # ZNLL 001; A-side Matrix # ZNLL 001
          Lowlands
          Antwerp, Belgium
        - Manzanera, Phil - Listen now, 1977; SR-19838; Manzanera, Phil; 801 (Box 346)
          Catalog # PD-1-6147; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6147 AS-CT
        - Manzanera, Phil - Listen now, 1997; SR-19839; Manzanera, Phil; 801 (Box 346)
          Catalog # EGLP 30; A-side Matrix # EGLP-30-A
          Editions EG
        - Manzanera, Phil - Listen now, 1977; SR-19840; Manzanera, Phil; 801 (Box 347)
          Catalog # 2302 074; A-side Matrix # 2302074 A//2
        - Manzanera, Phil - Listen now, 1977; SR-19841; Manzanera, Phil; 801 (Box 347)
          Catalog # 2310 571; A-side Matrix # 231057 1 A 520 211077
        - Manzel - It's over now, 2003; SR-19842; Manzel (Box 347)
          Catalog # DB-7004; A-side Matrix # DB 7004 A1
          Dopebrothers Records
        - Manzel - Space funk; Midnight theme, 2003; SR-19843; Manzel (Box 347)
          Catalog # DB-7003; A-side Matrix # DB-7003-B
        - Mapfumo, Thomas - Corruption, 1989; SR-19844; Mapfumo, Thomas; Blacks Unlimited (Box 347)
          Catalog # MLPS 9848; A-side Matrix # MLPS 9848 A-Z DMM
        - Mapfumo, Thomas - Hupenyu wangu (all my life), 1985; SR-19845; Mapfumo, Thomas; Blacks Unlimited (Box 347)
          Catalog # RTT 190; A-side Matrix # RTT 190 A-1U-1-1-1
          Rough trade
        - Mar-Keys - Back to back, 1967; SR-19846; Mar-Keys; Booker T & The MG's (Box 347)
          Catalog # S 720; A-side Matrix # ST-STX-671065-A
          Stax
        - Maranda, Andrée - (Love is like an) itchin' in my heart, 1987; SR-19847; Maranda, Andrée (Box 347)
          Catalog # NFS-1212; A-side Matrix # NFS-1212-RE1-A
          NFS Records, Inc
        - Marauder - Get loose Mother Goose; Terminator, 1987; SR-19848; Marauder; Fury (Box 347)
          Catalog # PA 011; A-side Matrix # PA-011-A
          Public Records
        - Marcel - Gambler's Delight (disc one), 2004; SR-19849; Marcel (Box 347)
          Catalog # CKMA002LP; A-side Matrix # CKMA 002
          Cookin' Records
        - Marcel - Gambler's Delight (disc two), 2004; SR-19850; Marcel (Box 347)
        - Marcel - Gambler's Delight (disc three), 2004; SR-19851; Marcel (Box 347)
        - Marchan, Bobby - Disco rabbit, 1977; SR-19852; Marchan, Bobby (Box 347)
          Catalog # MK-30; A-side Matrix # MK-30-3 2-53567-CT
        - Mari, Teairra - Roc-A-Fella Records Presents Teairra Marí (disc one), 2005; SR-19853; Mari, Teairra (Box 347)
          In same jacket as # SR-19854. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16407-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16407-1A
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - Mari, Teairra - Roc-A-Fella Records Presents Teairra Marí (disc two), 2005; SR-19854; Mari, Teairra (Box 347)
          In same jacket as # SR-19853. Double album.
          Catalog # DEFF 16408-1; A-side Matrix # DEFF-16408-1A
        - Mari, Teairra - Roc-A-Fella Records Presents Teairra Marí (disc one), 2005; SR-19855; Mari, Teairra (Box 347)
          In same jacket as # SR-19856. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004526-01; A-side Matrix # B0004526-01-A
        - Mari, Teairra - Roc-A-Fella Records Presents Teairra Marí (disc two), 2005; SR-19856; Mari, Teairra (Box 347)
          In same jacket as # SR-19855. Double album.
          Catalog # B0004526-01; A-side Matrix # B0004526-01-C
        - Mariachi - Desperado, 1996; SR-19857; Mariachi (Box 347)
          Catalog # DIG P-16; A-side Matrix # DIG P 16-A
          Dig It International
          Milan, Italy
        - Marillion - Warm wet circles (remix), 1987; SR-19858; Marillion (Box 347)
          Catalog # 12MARIL 8; A-side Matrix # 12MARIL 8 A-2-1-3
        - Mario - Just a friend (2002 remix), 2002; SR-19859; Mario (Box 347)
          Catalog # 80813-21176-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-21176-1S4
          J Records
        - Mario - Whip it baby!, 1990; SR-19860; Mario (Box 347)
          Catalog # IGU74005-1; A-side Matrix # RUM-200-A-RE-1
          Nastymix Records
          Seattle, Washington
        - Mario - C'mon, 2002; SR-19861; Mario (Box 347)
          Catalog # J1PV-21255-1; A-side Matrix # J1PV-21255-1SA
        - Mario - Let me love you, 2004; SR-19862; Mario (Box 347)
          Catalog # 82876-61888-1; A-side Matrix # 82876-61888-1 SA
        - Mark IV - It's a mean world, 1988; SR-19863; Mark IV (Box 347)
          Catalog # TUF 128032; A-side Matrix # TUF 128032-A
          Tuff City
        - Mark D and the OCC - Sadistic journalist EP, 1997; SR-19864; Mark D and the OCC (Box 347)
          Catalog # MDOCCRD; A-side Matrix # MDOCCRD-A
          Native Owned Record Label
          San Jose, California
        - Markay, Barbara - It's all rite to fuck all nite, 1979; SR-19865; Markay, Barbara (Box 347)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # FU-3
          Hot Box Records
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - I know, 1994; SR-19866; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 92-77103; A-side Matrix #
          Tuff Gong
          Jamaica
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Uprising, 1980; SR-19867; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 90036-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-825083-B
          Island Records
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Iron lion zion, 1992; SR-19868; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 12 TGX 2; A-side Matrix # 12 TGX 2 A1
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Rastaman vibration, 1976; SR-19869; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # ILPM 9383; A-side Matrix # ILPM 9383 A-2U
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Rastaman vibration, 1976; SR-19870; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # ILPM 9383; A-side Matrix # ILPM 9383 A-1
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Natty dread, 1974; SR-19871; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 90037-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-825085-A
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Catch a fire, 1973; SR-19872; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 90030-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-825071-A
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Keep on moving, 1980; SR-19873; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # PR12 6981-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 6981-1A HS
        - Marley, Bob - What goes arouns comes around, 1996; SR-19874; Marley, Bob (Box 347)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # JAD5001-A
          JAD Records
          Beverly Hills, California
        - Bob Marley & the Wailers - Legend: the best of Bob Marley and the Wailers, 1984; SR-19875; Bob Marley & the Wailers; Marley, Bob; Wailers (Box 347)
          Catalog # 90169-1; A-side Matrix # ST-IL-845507-A
        - Marley, Damian - Me name Jr. Gong, 1998; SR-19876; Marley, Damian; Grand Puba (Box 347)
          Catalog # 54240-0; A-side Matrix # 54240-0 A
        - Marley, Damian - Searching (so much bubble) the ragga mixes, SR-19877; Marley, Damian (Box 347)
          Catalog # PRLP 3032; A-side Matrix # PRLP 3032A
        - Marley, Damian - Welcome to jamrock, 2005; SR-19878; Marley, Damian (Box 347)
          Catalog # UNIR 21503-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21503-1A
        - Marl, Marley - The symphony, 1988; SR-19879; Marl, Marley (Box 347)
          Catalog # 0-21124; A-side Matrix # 0-21124A SR1
        - Marley, Richie - Jump dem, SR-19880; Marley, Richie; Marley, Bob (Box 347)
          Catalog # NM-1001; A-side Matrix # 1001-A
          Nine Mile America
          Coconut Groove, Florida
        - Marley, Rita - Who colt the game, 1990; SR-19881; Marley, Rita (Box 347)
          Catalog # SHANACHIE 6016; A-side Matrix # SH-6016-A
          Shanachie Records
          Newton, New Jersey
        - Marley, Rita - Good girls culture, 1985; SR-19882; Marley, Rita (Box 347)
          Catalog # SHANACHIE-5013; A-side Matrix # SH-5013-A